Do pick up a new support
Crap
Love
Why
Yeah
What 10 varieties are there?
It's fun!
It's a little off, but it's lunch time,
so I'm going to order some food.
Today's lunch is a delivery.
I was thinking of putting the menu on
the table, but I thought I'd take a
video.
I'm going to order food.
Have you ever played the earphone gun
game?
I've played it a few times.
If you tell the person who orders the
food what you want to eat, you can eat
what you want to eat.
There are five people today, so I'll do
it five times.
The first thing I want you to decide is
that only the person who orders the food
will decide by rock-paper-scissors.
The person who decides the order can
write what they want to eat.
So, you're going to play rock-paper-
scissors, and the winner will decide
today's lunch.
I'm sure I'll get what I want to eat.
There's a leader like that here.
You don't have to be a leader.
I'm going to decide who can hide what I
want to eat first.
It's important.
I'm sure I'll get what I want to eat.
Rock-paper-scissors!
Yato-san!
I don't want to see it anymore.
I'm going to do it.
I did it.
Today's order is from Fujitani.
I'll give you the memo and the menu.
You can order what you want to eat
first.
I can order what I want to eat, right?
Yes, you can.
Don't say what you want to eat while
choosing.
I see.
Excuse me.
What should I order?
What should I do?
Don't sing because you have a
copyright.
I see.
I'll order what I want to eat.
What should I do?
I'll order it.
Mago shore rice and
Mago shore rice
Oolong tea
Mago and rice
Rice
And oolong tea
Mago and rice
Oolong tea
Thank you for watching!
Stir-fried Lebanese sausage set meal
and
lunch
Wow, you are fast
Stir-fried Lebanese sausage set meal
and
lunch
Uron-chan
Stir-fry the lebanese sauce
and eat it
Please subscribe to my channel!
and
Oolong tea
Tebanira
Tegata
Plain and Oolong tea
I've never seen such a tension
I'm so happy.
Te-ba-ni-ra
Oh?
Te-ba-ni-ra?
Never mind.
Te-ba-ni-ra
Te-ga-ta
Teishoku
To-uron-cha
I'm so happy.
Te-ba-ni-ra
Te-ga-ta
Teishoku
To-uron-cha
In the morning
Mago-don and o-run-cha
Please subscribe to my channel.
Udon.
Correct.
Yeah!
Stir-fried shrimp with chili sauce.
Correct.
I can't remember the name.
Shrimp stir-fried seafood.
Shrimp stir-fried with shiso.
I can't remember the name.
Shrimp stir-fried with chili sauce.
A scaffold appears!
I'm going to order pizza.
I think you've heard the order.
Please order the menu you want to eat.
I'll do my best.
Don't forget to order.
I got it.
I'll call you.
Pizza is here.
I'm kidding.
Hello.
I'd like to order.
I'd like to order dumplings, egg soup,
mapo tofu and oolong tea.
I'd like vanilla ice cream and salad.
Yes.
I'd like to have a pear.
I'd like a crab ball.
I'd like another mapo tofu.
I'd like rice and fried shrimp.
I'd like spring rolls.
Thank you for watching this video.
Please subscribe to this channel.
I need a receipt.
I need a receipt for my start-up
promotion.
I got it.
I need a receipt for the price.
I need to take two pictures.
Please subscribe to this channel.
Thank you.
Excuse me.
I'm done.
I'm worried.
I've been standing for a long time.
You looked so serious.
I was worried.
When you receive the letter, you can
give it to the person who wrote it.
I see.
I'm going to give it to the person who
wrote it.
Please subscribe to this channel.
I'm going to bring the food to you.
Thank you.
I don't think so.
I put it in front of you.
You can't open it.
I can't open it.
Why did you open it?
I'll take it off.
You're not good at it.
Show me your best.
I can't hold it.
I'm sorry.
There is a menu that you should have
ordered in front of you.
I'm hungry.
I'm happy to be hungry.
You'll open your eyes later.
Please leave your impressions.
Fujitani will announce the menu and
answer.
Please open your eyes and check the
menu.
This is a big meal.
Fujitani will announce the menu.
Hikaru will announce the menu.
Shrimp chili noodles.
Yuna will announce the menu.
There is no rice.
I didn't order rice.
Karen will announce the menu.
There is no toaster.
I was told that there is no salad.
I thought it was crab.
There is no toaster.
So, I chose spring roll.
What? I chose tofu and green tea.
Mabo and green tea.
I chose mabo don.
Yuna chose mabo fried rice.
This is the worst.
I chose Lebanese set meal and oolong
tea.
Please subscribe to this channel.
It's not a hand vanilla.
It's a hand vanilla and a hand-shaped
one.
Let's eat.
Look at this amount of lotus root.
It's a lot.
You shouldn't eat it alone.
Please give me alcohol.
I'll enjoy it.
Let's eat.
I thought it would be better to order
Tenshinhan.
Let's order Kani-Tama.
We are going to eat only what we
ordered.
What was the expression you made?
I said there is no salad.
I said Haruma-Ten.
I see.
I was surprised.
I don't know what Oolong tea is.
What does it mean?
I heard Oolong tea is a type of tea.
I see.
I heard it is a type of tea.
I want to give you Oolong tea, but I
can't.
Thank you.
You haven't eaten anything.
I ate meat.
Really?
I ate liver.
I ate it.
Did you eat it?
I'm so happy.
You ate everything you could eat.
I ate liver.
You ate liver.
I ordered liver, but I ate only liver.
I'll eat it later.
You ordered everything you could eat.
I did.
I ate a lot.
I ate liver.
Please tell us your feelings after the
video.
I'm glad I said that.
Thank you for watching this video.
See you next Monday.
Next Monday.
We're ITZY.
Thank you for watching this video.
Bye bye.